Finding aid to Association for Intercollegiate Athletics for Women records SSC.MS.00584
Sophia Smith Collection
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: NCAA Testimony -- Toner (Box 21)
- NCAA v. AIAW Transcription, 1977 (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Baker (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Blackburn (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Brown (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- De Varona (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Fritz (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Grant (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Hunt (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Koch (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony -- Lardner (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Lopiano (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Mason (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Morrison (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Murray (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Taylor (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Tietz (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Uhlir (Box 22)
- AIAW Litigation – AIAW v. NCAA: AIAW Testimony (continued) -- Watson (Box 22)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews -- Pleadings: Volume 1 of 3 (Index #s 1-34) (Box 22)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- Pleadings: Volume 2 of 3 (Index #s 35a-53) (Box 22)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- Pleadings: Volume 3 of 3 (Index #s 54-71) (Box 22)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- Motions to Dismiss (Box 23)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (Box 23)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- Amicus Curiae Materials (Box 23)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- Motion to Intervene (Box 23)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- Summary Judgment: Pre-Answer, Volume 1 of 2 (Box 23)
- AAHPER NCAA v. Mathews (continued) -- Oral Argument Transcript, April 11, 1977 (Box 23)
- AIAW Litigation – NCAA v. Califano -- Oral Argument, Jan 22, 1980 (Box 23)
- AIAW Litigation – NCAA v. Califano -- Original Pleadings File, 1978 (Box 23)
- AIAW Litigation – NCAA v. Califano -- Briefs and Replies Filed with Court (Box 23)
- AIAW Litigation – NCAA v. Califano -- Main File (Box 23)
- AIAW Litigation – NCAA v. Califano -- Index, 1978-83 (Box 23)
- AIAW Litigation -- University of Alaska (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation -- University of Alaska Discovery File (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation -- AIAW v. Sugarman, 1978-80 (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation -- California State – Fullerton: Main File (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation (continued) -- NCAA v. Amateur Athletic Union, 1977-78 (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation (continued) -- Estes v. AIAW, 1981 (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation (continued) -- AIAW v. University of Connecticut, 1981 (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation (continued) -- University of Illinois, Champaign, 1977-78 (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation (continued) -- Calabrese v. University of Illinois, undated (Box 24)
- AIAW Litigation (continued) -- Julie Brown v. AIAW, 1978-79 (Box 24)
- AIAW: NCAA -- Subcommittee on Oversight & Investigations Hearings, 1978 (Box 25)
- AIAW: NCAA -- Convention, 1981-82 (Box 25)
- AIAW: NCAA -- Special Investigation, 1981 (Box 25)
- AIAW: NCAA -- General, May 1981 (Box 25)
- AIAW RMP -- Ghostings & Position Memoranda, 1978 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships -- Championship Declarations, 1981 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships -- CCNC – Seeding & Selection Appeals, 1981-82 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships -- Committee to Study Qualifying Route, 1979-81 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships -- Sports Committee Operating Code, 1976-77 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships -- Committee on Conduct of National Champs., 1979-81 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Standard Contract, 1976-81 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Badminton, 1978-81 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Basketball, 1975-81 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Cross Country, 1977 (Box 25)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Fencing, 1979-81 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Field Hockey, 1975-82 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Golf, 1979-82 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Gymnastics, 1975-82 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Lacrosse, 1980-81 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Skiing, 1977-80 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Softball, 1969-81 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Swimming and Diving, 1975-82 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Tennis, 1977-82 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Track and Field, 1975-82 (Box 26)
- AIAW National Championships (continued) -- Volleyball, 1977-81 (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- Pre-1966 CIAW-DGWS, 1962-1966 (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- Pre-1966 NCAA, 1962-1966 (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- Pre-1966 Misc., 1962-1966 (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1966 CIAW-DGWS (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1966 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1966 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1967 CIAW-DGWS (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1967 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1967 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1968 CIAW-DGWS (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1968 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1968 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1969 CIAW-DGWS (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1969 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1969 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1970 AIAW-CIAW (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1970 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1970 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1971 AIAW-CIAW (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1971 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1972 AIAW-CIAW (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1972 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1972 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1973 AIAW (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1973 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1973 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1974 AIAW (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1974 NCAA (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1974 Misc. (Box 26)
- Correspondence -- 1975 AIAW (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1975 NCAA (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1975 Misc. (Box 27)
- AIAW Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1975-1979 (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1976 AIAW (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1976 NCAA (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1976 Misc. (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1977 AIAW (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1977 NCAA (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1977 Misc. (Box 27)
- Correspondence -- 1978 AIAW (Box 27)
- NCAA Council Minutes, Jan. 1974, Jan. 1976, Jan. 1978 (Box 28)
- NCAA Council Minutes, 1974-01 (Box 28)
- Memorandums (Box 28)
- Letters, Telex (Box 28)
- NCAA Executive Committee Excerpts (Minutes) (Box 28)
- Legal Actions (Box 28)
- NCAA Executive Committee Minutes - Table of Contents (Box 28)
- Convention Actions (Box 28)
- Council of Collegiate Women Athletic Administrators (Box 28)
- Executive Committee (Box 28)
- Standing Committees (Box 28)
- Articles, Television A-D (Box 28)
- AIAW-Related Memorandums/Memos (Box 28)
- Byers - Questions/Notes on NCAA Information, Memorandums, Analysis, and Data (Box 28)
- Correspondence -- 1978 NCAA (Box 28)
- Correspondence -- 1978 Misc. (Box 28)
- Correspondence -- 1979 AIAW (Box 28)
- Correspondence -- 1979 NCAA (Box 28)
- Correspondence -- 1979 Misc. (Box 28)
- AIAW International Athletics - USOC Legislation Committee, 1981 (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics - USOC Executive Board Meeting Colorado Springs, Jan. 25-27, 1980 (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics - USOC Executive Board Meeting Nashville TN, Nov. 21-23, 1980 (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics - USOC House of Delegates Meeting, 1980-04 (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics - USOC House of Delegates Meeting, Jan. 1981 (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics - USOC/LAOOC (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics - USOC/LAOOC Contract (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics - Women's Games (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Hatch Amendment S.6123 (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Higher Ed. Reauthorization Act - 1980: Hatch/Erlenborn Amendments (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Title IX-Related State Laws (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Title IX Amendments, 1977- (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC H.R. 12626 (Box 29)
- AIAW International Athletics: USOC Legislation Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC - H.R. 12626 - Testimony (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Need for/Feasibility of a National Study of Collegiate Athletics (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - NCAA (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Notes - Misc. (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Publications (Box 29)
- AIAW Legislation - Telephone Transcripts (Box 29)
- President's Commission on Olympic Sports - First Report, Feb. 1976 (Box 30)
- Final Report of President's Commission on Olympic Sports 1975-77 v. 1 (Box 30)
- Final Report of President's Commission on Olympic Sports 1975-77 v. 2 (Box 30)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC - S.2036 (Box 30)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC 2.2727 - Committee Report (Box 30)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC S.2036/S.2727 - Extra Staff Working Drafts (Box 30)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC S.2036/S.2727 (Box 30)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC S.2036/2727 - Hearing Trans. on 2036 (Box 30)
- AIAW Legislation - USOC - S.2036 Testimony (Box 30)
- AIAW Promotional - Broderick Company (Box 30)
- AIAW Promotional - Coca-Cola USA (Box 30)
- AIAW Promotional - Hanes Medalist BB/Classic, 1979 (Box 30)
- AIAW Promotional - Eastman Kodak Company (Box 30)
- AIAW Promotional - Promotions History (Box 30)
- AIAW Promotional - Tea Council of the U.S., Inc. (Box 30)
- AIAW Committees - Ad Hoc Committee to Study Recruiting (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Awards Contracts & Correspondence (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Constitution - C. Gordon (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Chief Executive Officers Council (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Committee on Sports Information Directors (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Committee on Committees
- AIAW Committees - Division III Financial Aid (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Division Structuring Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - AIAW - Division Structure (Donna) (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Divisional Implementation Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Final Impl. of AIAW Representation to Outside Governing Groups (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Fiscal Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Miscellaneous (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - International Competition Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Long Range Planning Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Media Relations Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Committee on Men's Athletics (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Committee on Status of Minority Women (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Nominating Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Presidential Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Promotions Committee, 1981 (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Prop. Committee to Study Automatic Championship Berths (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Publicity Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Resolutions Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Restrictive Rules Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Restructuring Committee (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - Rules Standards, 1981 (Box 31)
- AIAW Committees - TV Committees, 1981 (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - AAHPER (American Alliance) (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - Addresses and Phone Numbers (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - Articles of Incorporation (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - Merrily Baker - Personal File (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - Council of Collegiate Women Athletic Administration (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - College Athletic Placement Service (Bill Sera) (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - 14th National Conference on Women and the Law (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - Conflict of Interest (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - District of Columbia Tax Exemption Application (Box 31)
- AIAW Organizational - Decisions on Athletic Governance (Box 31)
- AIAW International Athletics - File #2 - Athletic Congress (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - Athletic Congress, 1979-1981 (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - ABAUSA, 1976-1981 (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - ABAUSA Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - Lacrosse (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - Rowing (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - TFA/USA (Track & Field Association) (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - USCSC (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - International Commission (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - Gymnastics (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - USFHA (Hockey) (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - PRC Tour, 1981 (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics - USTA (U.S. Tennis Association) (Box 32)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - Swimming (Box 33)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - USWF (Wrestling) (Box 33)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - USVBA (U.S. Volleyball Association) (Box 33)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - USOC: AAU/USOC (Box 33)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - USOC: Applications for Recognition as a National Governing Body (Box 33)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - USOC: Development Committee (Box 33)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - USOC General, 1979-1983 (Box 33)
- AIAW International Athletics (continued) - USOC - Eligibility (Box 33)
- AIAW: Professional Sports - Basketball (Box 33)
- AIAW: Professional Sports - Volleyball (Box 33)
- AIAW: Professional Sports - Professional Sports Committee (Box 33)
- AIAW: Professional Sports - Softball (Box 33)
- AIAW Informational - Background: Women in Sports (Box 33)
- AIAW Informational - Background, News Clippings, Articles, Jan. 1979— (Box 33)
- AIAW Informational - AIAW Statistics (Box 33)
- AIAW Informational - Wilhoite v. Big Eight Conference (Box 33)
- AIAW Organizational - Employment Discrimination (Box 33)
- AIAW Organizational - Executive Board (Box 33)
- AIAW Organizational - Executive Committee, 1983 (Box 33)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Executive Committee, 1982 (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Executive Secretary Search, 1979 (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Christine Grant — President-Elect (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Handbook, 1980-1981 (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - High School Brochure (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - High School Federation (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Insurance (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Internal Organization (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Interregnum File (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - IRS Application 501(c)(3) (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Letters of Intent, 1979-1981 (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Letters of Intent, 1982 (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - National Coalition, 1982 (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Carole Mushier Personal (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics (N.A.C.D.A.) (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - N.A.G.W.S. 1981— (Box 34)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Donna Lopiano (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Membership Mailings (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Lee Morrison (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - AIAW/NAIA (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - National Coalition, 1981 (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - National Coalition - Coalition of Women's Groups on Appointments (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - National Junior College Athletic Association (NJCAA) (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Executive Committee, 1981 (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - National Office Site (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - National Student Exchange Program (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Newsletters (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - N. Christian College AA (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Carole A. Oglesby, Temple U. Sports Car. Bd. (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Org. of Dir. of Women's Athletics at Big 8 Institutions (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Photographs (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - PR & Promotions — Director (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - President's File, 1979 (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - President's File, 1980 (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Championships, 1979-1980 (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Council (Box 35)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #1 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs & Materials - #2 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #3 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #4 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #5 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #6 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #7 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #8 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Regional Regs. & Materials - #9 (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Seibert Survey (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Slatton, Bonnie (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Stamp (Commemorative) (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Student Involvement (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Surveys (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Tax Exemptions: D.C. Real Prop. & Personal Prop. Tax Exempt. Appl. (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Trademark (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Travel Agreements (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Ann Uhlir (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Women's Athletic Directors Group (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Women's Basketball Coaches Association (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Women's College World Series of Omaha Inc. (WCWS Inc.) (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Women's Educational Equity Act (Box 36)
- AIAW Organizational (continued) - Women's Sports Foundation (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Athletic Guidelines (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Cannon v. University of Chicago (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Complaint against Arizona State University (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Complaint against Arkansas Activ. Association (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Complaint against Colgate University (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Complaint against Furman U. (Greenville, South Carolina) (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Complaint against Grove City College (Box 36)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against Hillsdale College (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against Marian College (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against Mid-American Conference (MAC) (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against Michigan State University (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against Southern ILL University (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against Temple University (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against University of Florida (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against University of Georgia (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against University of Louisville (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against University of Michigan (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Complaint against University of Minnesota (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Consulting Services on Compliance (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Correspondence (R&P) Interpretations (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - DeHart Associates (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Florida State University Survey Materials (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - General, 1981 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - HEW Final Policies (General), 1979 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - HEW Final Policies (Clipping & Background), 1979 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - HEW Relations General, 1977 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - HEW Relations Athletics, 1977 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Title IX — General (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - HEW Policies/Interpretations, 1979 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Letter to Libassi - Meeting, 1979 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Legislation, 1981-1982 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Sanford Plan (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Title IX/Athletics - Briefing Paper M.P. Draft, 1979-06 (Box 37)
- AIAW Title IX Administration (continued) - Title IX Compliance (Box 37)
- Renouf & Polivy - Correspondence, Memos, Agreements (Box 38)
- Original AIAW Trademark Registration (Box 38)
- AIAW/NBC Contract, 1979 (Box 38)
- AIAW/NBC Letter Agreement (Box 38)
- AIAW/Nissen Trophy Agreement, 1980 (Box 38)
- AIAW/NIKE Agreement, 1980 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Louisville Slugger Agreement, 1980 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Sports & Leisure International Agreement, 1980 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Wilson Sporting Goods Contract, 1980-1982 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Sauk Valley Agreement, Field Hockey Manual, 1980-1983 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Nissen Agreement (VB Champs Divs I, II, III), 1980-1982 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Russell (Volleyball All-America Program Div. I), 1980 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Owens 1980-1981 Champ. Trophies Contract (Box 38)
- AIAW/Black Knight Enter. Agreement (Badminton Manual), 1980-1983 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Louisville Badminton Supply Contract, 1981-1983 (Box 38)
- AIAW/New Balance Indoor Track & Field Program Agreement, 1980 (Box 38)
- AIAW/De Beer Slow Pitch Softball Agreement, 1981 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Gym Master K (Div. I, II, III Gymnastics Championships), 1980 (Box 38)
- AIAW/Kodak 1981-1983 Contract (Signed 12/30/80 by Ann Uhlir), 1980 (Box 38)
- Title IX Materials (Box 38)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - OCR: Department of Education (Box 38)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Title IX Info (put out by AIAW) (Box 38)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - OCR Title IX Athletic Policy Task Force (Box 38)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Title IX Intercollegiate Athletics Investigator's Manual (Box 38)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - Title IX Manual Drafts (Box 38)
- AIAW Title IX Administration - U.S. Commission in Civil Rights (Box 38)
- Letter - Mary Lou Enberg to Sam Jankovich (Box 38)
- Research - Women and Athletic Policy in the 1920s (Box 38)
- DVD - Photographs of 2009 AIAW Reunion (Box 38)
- Duplicate Materials, 1975-1981 (Box 39)
  Appraisal
  Duplicate materials which will be removed from collection pending deed of gift.